http://www.cruisereport.com/privacy

Home/
Reviews/Cruise ReviewsHotel ReviewsCruise BlogsTravel ProductsAttractionsCruise Ship DiningArticles
Cruise News/
Privacy Policy
Home/
Reviews/Cruise ReviewsHotel ReviewsCruise BlogsTravel ProductsAttractionsCruise Ship DiningArticles
Cruise News/
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site.When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: username, a valid e-mail address and password. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To confirm, by email, any review submissions you post to the websiteYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.How do we protect your information? We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. Your name and email address are protected through the use of a username and password that you create when you set up your account.We do not collect or storesensitive personal information such as credit cards or social security numbers.Do we use cookies? Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties? We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transferto outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party links Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. For example, a link to a cruise line website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Settings' page.Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy Only This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and Conditions Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at Your Consent By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy Policy If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on March 1, 2015Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: http://www.cruisereport.cominfo@cruisereport.com
Home/
Reviews/Cruise ReviewsHotel ReviewsCruise BlogsTravel ProductsAttractionsCruise Ship DiningArticles
Cruise News/
CruiseReport.com
About Us
Hi, we are Chris and Rickee and we have been cruise journalists since 2002. We love sharing our cruise adventures with you.
Read more
CRUISEREPORT.COM is a registered trademark of PITA, LLC.Copyright ©2002-2021 PITA, LLC dba CruiseReport. All rights reserved.
